there was this one time I had a really
good date with this girl so I got home
and I was like I'm going to look at her
Spotify
profile it's an important step because
when I look at her Spotify I get to see
if we share the same taste in music or
if I need to start the process of
convincing myself that I like her
[Laughter]
music and I can do either one I have no
preference done both many times before
but I'm going through her profile on
Spotify and I see she has an entire
Bruce Springsteen playlist and Bruce one
of my all-time favorite artists and I
start freaking out I'm like she's the
one but then I scroll up and I noticed
it's actually her dad's
playlist that she's just following it's
like oh what do I do with those feelings
I just
had
yeah